What a day!
It's gorgeous!
As long as we can stay on this heading,
we should reach the marine
base in no time at all!
Wow, Kobe, you're great out here!
You mean we're actually gonna reach
the place we originally set out for?
Of course, it's nothing.
I'm just using the skills
that every sailor should have.
You know, there's really
nothing to be so giggly about,
because at the marine base, they're
holding the great pirate hunter.
Roronoa Zoro
This is the man who's diced up his
bounties like an animal bent on
carnage A bloodthirsty beast He's been
called nothing less than a living,
breathing demon in human form?
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real?
Through it all, through
all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on the cruise.
We are.
We're here!
The marine base city!
Luffy, seriously,
you're out of your mind if you think the
right thing to do is get
this guy to join you.
Well, I haven't made up my mind yet.
I gotta see if he's a good guy.
He's imprisoned because
he's obviously not!
Hey, is that guy Zoro
around here somewhere?
Maybe we shouldn't mention
the name Zoro here, okay?
Let's head to the base and check it out.
You want to be a marine, right?
Well, of course I do, Luffy, but I
really don't think I'm ready just yet.
From what I've heard, the man in charge
of this base is named Captain Morgan.
This town is such a weird
place! That was odd.
I mean, I understand if
they're scared of Zoro,
but why did they flip when I
mentioned the marine captain's name?
I don't know.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Maybe they were all just jumping
around for the fun of it.
And how would that make any sense?
This looks like the place!
I made it.
This is where you and I part ways, Lou.
We didn't have long together, but...
Where's the foothold?
Get down from there!
What are you doing?
They'll see you!
Now where's this demon?
They wouldn't keep him out in the open.
He's probably tucked in a
prison cell below ground.
There he is!
I'm gonna get closer.
Kobe, look!
I'm telling you, he's not...
That foot on his head.
and a Haramaki.
It's Frollo no Masira.
If we untie those ropes,
he can just walk away.
Oh, don't be such an idiot, Luffy.
There's no telling what a banyan
like him will do if you let him go.
He might just kill us both.
Don't worry, I'm strong.
I can protect us.
He's lost his mind.
Hey, you two.
You're an eyesore.
Get lost.
Oofy, trust me, there's no chance to
survive with someone like him on your crew!
Oofy, we've got to stop her!
She'll be killed either by the
Marines or the demon himself!
What do you want?
I thought you might be getting hungry
now, so I made you a couple of rice balls.
You got a death wish, kid? Just scram.
But you haven't eaten anything the
whole time you've been tied up.
Here.
I've never really made them before.
But I did my best, so
I think they're fine.
Listen, kid, I'm not hungry.
Now stop irritating me
and get out of here.
But...
Do not make me kick your ass, little girl!
Now, now, no one likes a bully.
Robo Noah Zoro, you seem
to be handling this well.
Don't you agree?
Hey, look, now there's another weird guy.
That's great.
He must be with the Marines.
Now we know the girl will be safe.
Lock, some tasty rice balls.
That's not for you!
Too sweet!
They're packed with sugar!
You're supposed to use salt, you idiot!
Salt! But I...
I thought they'd taste better sweet.
Give me that!
No, stop!
I worked so hard!
That's just awful!
But I worked so hard to
make those too bad you
must have not read the
notice that was posted.
Those who assist criminals in any way will
be executed signed marine captain morgan.
It seems even little
brats fear my daddy his
daddy so that guy's father
is captain morgan. You!
Toss this kid out, right now!
I said, throw her over the wall, soldier!
Now, if you won't follow my orders, I'll
tell my father. Yes, sir! I'll do it!
No!
Thanks, mister!
Bepo!
Are you two okay?
What about you, little girl?
Are you alright?
Right?
I can't believe how
wretched a person he is!
Now where are you hurt?
Anywhere? Damn you.
You're just dead set on staying
alive, aren't you? That's right.
And I'm gonna make it to the
month without any problems.
Right!
Good luck with that!
Only ten days left!
Oh, you still assume you'll make
it to the end of those ten days!
How can that man be so cruel?
Luffy?
What the?
Where did he go?
So I hear you're a bad guy.
Are you still here?
You're stuck out here for all
the world to see and nothing.
Are you really all that strong?
Mind your own business.
If I were you, I'd probably
starve to death in three days.
I've got more spirit
than you could ever have.
Which is how I'm gonna
survive this ordeal.
This, I swear.
Ha!
What a weirdo.
Wait, hold on.
Could you pick that up for me?
You're gonna eat this?
Because it's mostly a ball of mud.
Shut up and give it to me!
Now!
Should have listened to me. It was good.
Thanks for the food.
Really?
That's right.
He ate every last grain of rice there was.
That's great!
I wonder if Zoro is really as evil as
everyone thinks that he is. He's not!
He's good, because he got
himself punished for us.
You're, uh, you're making no sense. Sorry.
It's that dumb Helmepo.
He's the son of Captain Morgan.
Step aside! Step aside!
Make way for my beautiful pet doggy!
Anyone who doesn't move,
I'll have executed!
Stop it! You mean nothing!
You, little girl!
Is there some kind of problem with
how my beloved dog is behaving?
Rick, put it down!
You don't want to get us in trouble!
AHHHHH! OOH!
He dies so down!
Elmepo keeps punching and
kicking him while he's tied up.
He's being so unfair!
I don't...
I don't know how to help him!
I see why you're upset.
I'm hungry!
Bring us whatever you got and
keep the check for yourself.
And bring me a bottle of your finest
moonshine or whatever crap you serve.
I'm trying to think of
something interesting to
do seeing as how I'm bored
out of my skull here.
I suppose I could execute Zoro
You just hit me! Ufi, no!
You can't hit him!
This guy is scum!
You actually hit me!
I am Captain Morgan's son, you know!
Yeah, like I care!
You'll care after he
executes you for this!
Why don't you just be a man and fight?
Mubi, just ease off some!
Why are you trying to get
on the Marine's bad side?
It made up my mind.
Today, Zoro joins my crew.
I am... great.
Yes, sir!
You're right, Captain Morgan, sir.
And yet the taxes we collect don't even
compare to my sheer degree of greatness.
Yes, right, sir.
I guess that the citizens' wallets
just aren't very deep these days, sir.
The issue at hand here is
the level of respect for me.
When you agree...
Daddy!
There's someone outside that I want you
to slaughter, and I want it done now!
you again don't you have things
to do i'll untie you but only
if you promise to join my crew
you're what i run a pirate crew
and i'm looking for people to
join up no way i never stooped to
joining up with a criminal screw
that business and what's wrong
with being a pirate they're
despicable like i never want to join
up with one oh come on give me
a break everyone already knows
you as some vicious bounty hunter
always out for blood people
can say whatever they want about
me but i've never done a single
thing in my life that i regret
i will make it through this
challenge and after that i'll
accomplish what i want yeah that's
great but i've already decided
that you're going to be on my crew
what you can't do that i hear
you're one of the best swordsmen
around well i am but that idiot
captain's son took mine away
guess i'll just have to go get it
back for you what so if you want
your sword you're just gonna
have to join my crew now you're
really pissing me off wait he's
actually gonna bust in there alone
that's it stop right there now stand it up
in one final pull well
dad are you gonna get
revenge on this guy or what i mean he just
outright struck me in
public you've never hit me
before why should he
be able to do you have
any remote ideas to why
i've never hit you well
is it because you think
i'm great no it's because
you're
a
stupid fool
who isn't even worth it
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
The only great one around here
is the man you call your father.
Which reminds me, I heard a rat
snuck into the crucifixion yard.
Yes, that's right, the little
girl, but I had her dealt with.
I hope that means killed.
No, I didn't kill her, she's just a kid.
You there, go into town,
find this girl and kill her.
But, sir, you can't be serious.
She's just a little girl, sir.
I don't care if she's a child or not.
Anyone who disobeys my
orders is a traitor.
No, sir, I can't do it.
Lieutenant!
You, you killed him!
My strength was what I used
to rise to the rank of captain
Listen, in this world,
titles are what matter.
That means by being the captain of this
base and the highest ranking officer,
I am the most superior person
as far as the eye can see.
This means that I do everything right.
Am I correct, men?
Sir, you are correct, sir!
Let's put killing the
girl on hold for now.
Observe, the greatest symbol
of my unending authority.
It took years to complete, but here it is.
Now stand it up!
Display my greatness at the top
of this base for all to see!
That's weird.
There's nobody here.
I gotta find that crazy idiot's son
and get Zoro's sword back for him.
Pullman, harder!
You there.
You bumped it.
Sounds like something's going on up there.
I'm sorry, sir. I was
reckless. I didn't mean it.
I consider the slightest scratch on this.
Nothing less than a traitorous
activity that's punishable by death.
Guess I should check it out.
Jump, jump, rocket!
You're perfect!
I took too far!
What is that thing?
It flew up from the ground! Got it!
Sorry about that.
Seize him and hold him so I can kill
him myself! Sir! Right away! That's him!
That's the guy!
He's the one who pushed me, Daddy!
Hey, that's you!
I've been looking for
you all over the place!
You have something that I
really need to get back!
Let me go!
Help that bow!
Do not let that man escape!
Captain, there's someone
in the crucifixion yard!
What?
I'm surrounded by traitors.
You have to get out of here, Zoro.
That maniac's gonna kill you
for what you're doing right now.
I can't stand to watch the
marines behave like this anymore.
A true marine should be honorable.
Look, kid, I can't leave.
I got ten days left.
And then they're...
Well, not quite.
They're gonna execute you tomorrow.
The what?
El Meppo never intended
to honor your agreement.
He planned on killing you from the start.
Which made Luffy really angry.
So we just knocked him out.
He did?
Now that the marines are mad,
they're dead set on catching Luffy.
Don't worry, I'm not going to ask
you to become a pirate, though.
But I hope you'll help them.
You have a lot of strength you can offer.
Luffy's the only person here who can
actually save you from execution.
And, of course, you're the only one here
who can save him from a very similar fate.
End of the line!
Okay, so tell me where Zoro's sword is.
I'll tell you, I promise.
Just please stop dragging
me across the carpet.
Fine, which way?
In my room, we just passed it.
Behind you on the left.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Oh, we gotta go all the way back.
Don't move.
Except for letting Helmepo go. No way.
You can try shooting me if you want.
No, please don't shoot.
Get the hell out of the way.
For the crime of treason against me, I
sentence you both to die where you stand.
This looks like yours.
Bingo!
Hold on, there are three here.
Hey weirdo, which one of these is Serious?
I see passed out.
Kobe!
You've been pulling some
interesting moves around here.
What is this?
Some kind of poorly executed coup?
You two planned with the Straw Hat?
I've always fought alone
like a real man does,
not like a coward who hides behind
his wall of expendable cronies.
Roronoa Saru, don't you
dare underestimate me.
You may be a strong fighter,
But under my authority,
you're just a rat we throw
out with the trash. Take aim!
No.
I can't afford to die here.
Match over!
And the winner, Conney, with
2,000 total wins and zero losses.
Damn it!
You're weak, Zoro.
Nothing ever changes.
You know, for a boy, you're pathetic.
But Zoro isn't weak at all.
He's one of the strongest
out of all the guys.
He's even beaten grown-ups.
But he's nowhere as strong as me.
Even with two swords, a
weakling is still a weakling.
You losers would do good to
remember that and keep quiet.
Your howling makes you look even
more pitiful than you already are.
You've grown so strong, Zoro.
And yet, you continue to lose
every match against Kuina.
Sensei!
Are you getting her special training?
She might be her daughter,
but that's not fair!
You shouldn't cheat!
Calm down.
I've done nothing of the sort.
You see, Zoro has grown stronger.
But Kuina has continued
to grow stronger as well.
Zoro! Zoro?
I'm gonna go clean up.
Damn it!
Why can't I beat Clan? Why? Why?
I'm going to be the strongest swordsman
in the world, so why can't I beat her?
Thorough, it's laid
out. What are you doing?
Funny, I was gonna ask
you the same question.
What are you doing out so late?
I've come here to challenge
you to your City fight.
And it's gonna be the last
fight you and me will ever have.
This ends tonight.
Fight me with a real sword.
You do have one, don't you?
Real swords?
You're on.
I'm not
going to die.
Win, number 2001.
Damn it!
I hate it!
I'm the one who should be crying
out of frustration, not you.
When girls grow up,
it's natural for us to develop into
physically weaker beings than men.
Even you will catch up to me soon enough.
I've always heard you say to me, you're
going to be the world's greatest swordsman.
When I told my father the same
thing, he said I could never be that.
And I know, I know that, but
it's just so frustrating.
You're lucky, Zoro, being born as a man.
All I ever wanted was to be
the world's greatest swordsman.
My breasts have even
started to grow out now.
If only...
if I'd just been born a man!
Don't fly off in the mouth whining
like that after you beat me!
Because it's not fair!
You're my goal, you know
how this makes me feel?
Zoro.
Boy this, girl that,
are you going to keep up that same
kind of talk after I beat you someday?
Like skill is irrelevant!
That's just an insult to all of the
training I've been pouring on every day!
So don't say that crap, would ya?
Now promise me!
Promise me that someday one of us will
be the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll compete and see who gets there!
Dummy, you're so weak.
It's a promise.
Gotta get stronger so I
can hold lots of swords.
Two's not enough, I'll use three!
What do you guys want?
Kuina.
Kuina is dead, Zoro.
They said she slipped and fell
down the storehouse steps.
Storehouse?
Looking for a sharpening
stone for her beloved sword.
What would she need that for?
I don't know.
She was just a child, too.
Who knows why anyone does anything?
There's no way to rationalize it.
Guess you never know what's waiting
for you around the next corner.
It may appear otherwise to the blind
eye, But people are quite fragile things.
Sensei...
I ask that you let me have that sword.
Kawina's sword?
I'll get stronger!
Stronger than she ever was, you hear me?
Strong enough that my name
reaches up to the heavens!
I am going to be the
world's greatest swordsman!
I promised her!
I promised!
I did!
The sword is yours.
I leave her spirit and
her dreams in your hands.
Gum, gum, rocket! Fire!
What? Wolf, no! Straw Hat!
See ya!
That won't work on me!
Told you I was strong! What the?
Who the hell are you?
My name's Monkey D.
Luffy, and I'm gonna
be king of the pirates!
As a kid, I never stopped
searching for a great treasure.
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me.
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La la la la.
My only dream.
La la la la la.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But the world ever changes
as I call out your name.
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?
We'll be back.